Tufts-New England Medical Center Records MS224
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Planning office records, 1932 -- 1985; 1960 -- 1975; MS224.005; 31.2 Linear Feet
  - James Eacker files, 1961 -- 1980; MS224.005.007
    - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.044.00011; Tufts University School of Dental Medicine (Box 44)
    - Yesterday's Planning Won't Work in Today's Cities, 1969; MS224.005.044.00012; Field, Hermann H. (Box 44)
    - The Architects Collaborative, Inc., 1970; MS224.005.044.00013; Chas. T. Main, Inc. (Box 44)
    - T-NEMC Master Plan Report, 1970; MS224.005.044.00014; The Architects Collaborative; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 44)
    - T-NEMC parking facility and Eliot Street garage, 1969; MS224.005.044.00015 (Box 44)
    - Sprague daily employment report, parking garage, 1971; MS224.005.044.00016 (Box 44)
    - Proposal for the establishment of T-NEMC construction and related services, 1969; MS224.005.044.00017 (Box 44)
    - Sprauge - parking garage - requisitions and payments, etc., 1971 -- 1973; MS224.005.044.00018 (Box 44)
    - Sprauge garage - temporary bridge and and plaza, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.005.044.00019 (Box 44)
    - Phase II - neural sciences, MS224.005.044.00020 (Box 44)
    - Budget, 1971; MS224.005.044.00021 (Box 44)
    - Multi-temp hydronic oil fired heating plants engineering manual, MS224.005.044.00022 (Box 44)
    - Proposed site plan, 1980; MS224.005.044.00023 (Box 44)
  - South Cove files, 1957 -- 1972; MS224.005.008
    - South Cove - B.R.A. and T-NEMC tax summaries, MS224.005.044.00024 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Castle Square project, 1968; MS224.005.044.00025 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Chinese Benevolent Association, 1962; MS224.005.044.00026 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Chinese community, general, 1961; MS224.005.044.00027 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - T-NEMC property, 1960 -- 1965; MS224.005.044.00028 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - property adjustment original report, 1964; MS224.005.044.00029 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Chinese community housing, 1962; MS224.005.044.00030 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Bay Village, 1961; MS224.005.044.00031 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - property ownership, 1962; MS224.005.044.00032 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - site maps, MS224.005.044.00033 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Mr. Field's File, 1964 -- 1968; MS224.005.044.00034 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - A.B.C.D., 1962 -- 1964; MS224.005.044.00035 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Agencies Committee, 1962; MS224.005.044.00036 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Agencies Committee - turnpike relocation, 1962; MS224.005.044.00037 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Chinese community, Chinese Merchants' Association, MS224.005.044.00038 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - consultants, 1964; MS224.005.044.00039 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - council hearings, 1963; MS224.005.044.00040 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - developers, 1962; MS224.005.044.00041 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Chinese community Y.M.C.A., 1961 -- 1969; MS224.005.044.00042 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - disposition plan, MS224.005.044.00043 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Don Bosco development program, 1962; MS224.005.044.00044 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - educational program, Dental School, 1964; MS224.005.044.00045 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Eliot-Pearson Elementary School, MS224.005.044.00046 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - garment industry, 1962; MS224.005.044.00047 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - land users goals, 1962; MS224.005.044.00048 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - maps, MS224.005.044.00049 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - Massachusetts College of Art, 1961 -- 1962; MS224.005.044.00050 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - housing development, 1965; MS224.005.044.00051 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - housing - married student IBM code, MS224.005.044.00052 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - housing, MS224.005.044.00053 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - housing statistics, 1964 -- 1965; MS224.005.044.00054 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - housing relocation, 1962 -- 1964; MS224.005.044.00055 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - hotels - Bradford Hotel, 1957 -- 1961; MS224.005.044.00056 (Box 44)
    - I-B cost estimating, 1972; MS224.005.044.00057 (Box 44)
    - South Cove - project, MS224.005.045.00001 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - Chinese community, San Francisco, 1961; MS224.005.045.00002 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - Chinese community, turnpike relocation, 1962; MS224.005.045.00003 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - report covers, 1964; MS224.005.045.00004 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - Saint James R.C. Church, 1965; MS224.005.045.00005 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - Skid Row committee, 1962; MS224.005.045.00006 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - design projects thesis topics, MS224.005.045.00007 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - population, age and race, MS224.005.045.00008 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - parking, other institutions, MS224.005.045.00009 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - planning survey, 1961; MS224.005.045.00010 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - political representatives, MS224.005.045.00011 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - present parking, MS224.005.045.00012 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - Massachusetts Turnpike Authority, eminent domain, 1962; MS224.005.045.00013 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - Morgan Memorial Development Program, 1961; MS224.005.045.00014 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - NEMCH (adult) check move study, 1967; MS224.005.045.00015 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - newspaper publicity, T-NEMC area, 1962 -- 1965; MS224.005.045.00016 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - T-NEMC parking requirements, 1963 -- 1964; MS224.005.045.00017 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - T-NEMC housing proposals, 1961; MS224.005.045.00018 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - T-NEMC planning process, 1966; MS224.005.045.00019 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - T-NEMC programming schedule, 1965; MS224.005.045.00020 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - T-NEMC R.E. taxes, 1965; MS224.005.045.00021 (Box 45)
    - Urban Renewal - Government Center, 1963; MS224.005.045.00022 (Box 45)
    - Turnpike, 1966; MS224.005.045.00023 (Box 45)
    - South Cove - utility services discussion, 1964; MS224.005.045.00024 (Box 45)
    - South Cove, 1962; MS224.005.045.00025 (Box 45)
    - South Cove, 1962 -- 1963; MS224.005.045.00026 (Box 45)
  - Kay Opperman files, 1950 -- 1979; MS224.005.009
    - Budget, 1961 -- 1966; MS224.005.045.00027 (Box 45)
    - Rutgers essay, 1965 -- 1967; MS224.005.045.00028 (Box 45)
    - Forsyth speech, 1966; MS224.005.045.00029 (Box 45)
    - Extra copies of and conference invitations, 1969; MS224.005.045.00030 (Box 45)
    - Account numbers, extra copies, MS224.005.045.00031 (Box 45)
    - Telephone book submission, facilities development, 1971; MS224.005.045.00032 (Box 45)
    - HEW file by 20th of month, 1971; MS224.005.045.00033 (Box 45)
    - HEW reimbursements forms, 1971; MS224.005.045.00034 (Box 45)
    - Budget, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.005.045.00035 (Box 45)
    - Budget, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.045.00036 (Box 45)
    - Budget, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.045.00037 (Box 45)
    - Budget memo to administration committee, 1968; MS224.005.045.00038 (Box 45)
    - Budget, 1968 -- 1969; MS224.005.045.00039 (Box 45)
    - Budget, 1967 -- 1968; MS224.005.045.00040 (Box 45)
    - Budget, 1966 -- 1967; MS224.005.045.00041 (Box 45)
    - Office budget, 1961 -- 1964; MS224.005.045.00042 (Box 45)
    - Consultant fees, 1971; MS224.005.045.00043 (Box 45)
    - Expense accounts copies and original, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.045.00044 (Box 45)
    - Health Facilities Laboratory finances, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.045.00045 (Box 45)
    - Health Facilities Laboratorty contract, 1971; MS224.005.045.00046 (Box 45)
    - Expense account, Pollack, 1971; MS224.005.045.00047 (Box 45)
    - H.F.L. budget and staffing estimates, 1970; MS224.005.045.00048 (Box 45)
    - HFR preliminary final statement, 1972; MS224.005.045.00049 (Box 45)
    - T-NEMC planning Coonamessett Conference minutes, 1970; MS224.005.045.00050 (Box 45)
    - Expense account, Maloney, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.045.00051 (Box 45)
    - HFR bank statements, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.045.00052 (Box 45)
    - HFR Inc., memos, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.045.00053 (Box 45)
    - Oppermann, 1962; MS224.005.045.00054 (Box 45)
    - Temporary help, 1971; MS224.005.045.00055 (Box 45)
    - HFR task force expenses, MS224.005.045.00056 (Box 45)
    - Charges for HFL personnel, 1971; MS224.005.045.00057 (Box 45)
    - Expense account, Kay Opperman, 1971; MS224.005.045.00058 (Box 45)
    - HFL miscellaneous expenses, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.045.00059 (Box 45)
    - Accounts payable HFL, 1971; MS224.005.045.00060 (Box 45)
    - Paid checks 1-30, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.045.00061 (Box 45)
    - Washington telephone calls, 1971; MS224.005.045.00062 (Box 45)
    - Telephone calls for Washington meeting, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.045.00063 (Box 45)
    - Telephone calls for Yale Club, MS224.005.045.00064 (Box 45)
    - Letters with project proposals, MS224.005.045.00065 (Box 45)
    - HFL miscellaneous expenses, 1971; MS224.005.045.00066 (Box 45)
    - HFL schedules and agenda, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.045.00067 (Box 45)
    - Travel overseas, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.045.00068 (Box 45)
    - Distribution of Andover workbook, 1968; MS224.005.045.00069 (Box 45)
    - Andover conference #2, 1968; MS224.005.045.00070 (Box 45)
    - List of people invited to Andover conference, 1968; MS224.005.045.00071 (Box 45)
    - Andover conference minutes - statements, 1968; MS224.005.045.00072 (Box 45)
    - Greater NY-Illinois speech for Dr. Calisti, 1968; MS224.005.045.00073 (Box 45)
    - Tab statements - wire solved issues, 1968; MS224.005.045.00074 (Box 45)
    - Andover conference program and schedule, 1969; MS224.005.045.00075 (Box 45)
    - Andover conference replies to invitiations, 1969; MS224.005.045.00076 (Box 45)
    - Andover conference steering committee, 1969; MS224.005.045.00077 (Box 45)
    - Health Services Research Center application ambulatory care, 1968; MS224.005.045.00078 (Box 45)
    - Role of Dental School in Delivery of Health Care, 1969; MS224.005.045.00079; Calisti, Louis J.P. (Box 45)
    - Old times sheets, MS224.005.045.00080 (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous Calisti speeches, 1969; MS224.005.045.00081 (Box 45)
    - Grants, 1968; MS224.005.045.00082 (Box 45)
    - Expense account - Field, 1971; MS224.005.045.00083 (Box 45)
    - Symbiosis, MS224.005.045.00084 (Box 45)
    - Comprehensive Health Care - A Challenge to the Profession, 1968; MS224.005.045.00085 (Box 45)
    - T-NEMC authorization for change in construction or design, 1971 -- 1979; MS224.005.045.00086 (Box 45)
    - NEMCH organization chart, 1970; MS224.005.046.00001 (Box 46)
    - Extra set of change proposals for Dental Health Sciences Building sent to HEW, 1972; MS224.005.046.00002 (Box 46)
    - Minutes to be written up, 1966 -- 1968; MS224.005.046.00003 (Box 46)
    - Moving information, 1971; MS224.005.046.00004 (Box 46)
    - Hower, 1968; MS224.005.046.00005 (Box 46)
    - Hammer, William, 1966 -- 1969; MS224.005.046.00006 (Box 46)
    - Beckman, Richard, 1967 -- 1968; MS224.005.046.00007 (Box 46)
    - Colmeyer, Stephen, 1970; MS224.005.046.00008 (Box 46)
    - Dozier, Phillip, MS224.005.046.00009 (Box 46)
    - Laffoley, Paul, MS224.005.046.00010 (Box 46)
    - Lesser, Stephen, MS224.005.046.00011 (Box 46)
    - Lombard, Ruth Ann, 1969; MS224.005.046.00012 (Box 46)
    - Mason, John, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.005.046.00013 (Box 46)
    - Musolino, Ruth Ann, 1967; MS224.005.046.00014 (Box 46)
    - Nolan, Jay, 1967; MS224.005.046.00015 (Box 46)
    - Norris, Charles, 1968; MS224.005.046.00016 (Box 46)
    - Ogami, Susan, 1969; MS224.005.046.00017 (Box 46)
    - Ogilvie, Douglas, 1966 -- 1970; MS224.005.046.00018 (Box 46)
    - Parker, John, MS224.005.046.00019 (Box 46)
    - Mrs. Pike, 1970; MS224.005.046.00020 (Box 46)
    - Pounders, Betty, 1970; MS224.005.046.00021 (Box 46)
    - Ruggino, Richard, 1968 -- 1971; MS224.005.046.00022 (Box 46)
    - YEP replacement req, 1969; MS224.005.046.00023 (Box 46)
    - Zygas, Paul, 1967; MS224.005.046.00024 (Box 46)
    - Personnel passive, MS224.005.046.00025 (Box 46)
    - Reports for J.J. Sullivan, 1971; MS224.005.046.00026 (Box 46)
    - J.J. Sullivan - HEW, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.046.00027 (Box 46)
    - HEW - Washington D.C. - reports for grants officer construction progress and claims for reimbursement, 1971; MS224.005.046.00028 (Box 46)
    - Mrs. Opperman, 1970; MS224.005.046.00029 (Box 46)
      Budget information
    - HEW contruction cost and contract summary, 1971; MS224.005.046.00030 (Box 46)
    - Barr and Barr workmen's compensation, 1971; MS224.005.046.00031 (Box 46)
    - Carter, Susan, 1968; MS224.005.046.00032 (Box 46)
    - HEW report forms, 1971; MS224.005.046.00033 (Box 46)
    - NEMCH 1-A, MS224.005.046.00034 (Box 46)
    - Authorizations and agreements (1 of 2), 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.046.00035 (Box 46)
    - Authorizations and agreements (2 of 2), 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.046.00036 (Box 46)
    - Drawings - Rehabilitation roof and 5th floor, 1969; MS224.005.046.00037 (Box 46)
    - Letters and memos, 1967 -- 1969; MS224.005.046.00038 (Box 46)
    - Transmittals, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.005.046.00039 (Box 46)
    - Material not dated, MS224.005.046.00040 (Box 46)
    - Equipment pamphlets, 1950 -- 1967; MS224.005.046.00041 (Box 46)
    - Summary: education space estimates, 1963; MS224.005.046.00042 (Box 46)
    - Letters and memos - Joint Application, 1969; MS224.005.046.00043 (Box 46)
    - General documents and technical specifications for New England driving, 1968; MS224.005.046.00044 (Box 46)
    - Reports of Director of Planning, 1962 -- 1967; MS224.005.046.00045 (Box 46)
    - Reports of Planning Office - Correspondence, 1968; MS224.005.046.00046 (Box 46)
    - T-NEMC planning committee meeting, 1969; MS224.005.046.00047 (Box 46)
  - Publications, 1961 -- 1985; MS224.005.010
    - Problems of Pediatric Hospital Design, 1962 -- 1965; MS224.005.049.00001 (Box 49)
    - Applications of Computer Graphics in Community Mental Health Planning, 1969; MS224.005.049.00002 (Box 49)
    - Medical Centre Planning and Design within the Total Urban Setting, 1970; MS224.005.049.00003 (Box 49)
    - T-NEMC Land Building Space Inventory Summary of Floor Space by Department, 1962; MS224.005.049.00004 (Box 49)
    - South Cover Urban Renewal Project Area Survey of Functional Districts, 1962; MS224.005.049.00005 (Box 49)
    - Mental Health Coupling Project Interim Report, 1968; MS224.005.050.00001 (Box 50)
    - Properties Within Medical Center Development Area, 1965; MS224.005.050.00002 (Box 50)
    - Report on Housing Demand at T-NEMC, 1970; MS224.005.050.00003 (Box 50)
    - Study of Existing Facilities and New Possibilities for the Boston Dispensary, 1962; MS224.005.051.00006 (Box 51)
    - Notes from a Tour of Medical Facilities in the Midwest, 1963; MS224.005.051.00007 (Box 51)
    - A Proposal for a New Program in Medical Education at Tufts University Medical School, 1968; MS224.005.051.00008 (Box 51)
    - Quincy School Project Year One Final Report, 1966 -- 1967; MS224.005.051.00009 (Box 51)
    - Coupling Mental Health Services into the Community General Hospital System, 1967; MS224.005.051.00010 (Box 51)
    - Tufts Survey of Dental Practice, 1970; MS224.005.051.00011 (Box 51)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center Phase 1A, 1970 -- 1980; MS224.005.051.00012 (Box 51)
    - Preliminary Housing Market Analysis, 1961; MS224.005.051.00013 (Box 51)
    - Publications, 1966 -- 1970; MS224.005.051.00014 (Box 51)
    - New Dimension in Urban Renewal, 1968; MS224.005.051.00015 (Box 51)
    - Setting of Hospital Design, 1967; MS224.005.051.00016 (Box 51)
    - Effects of the Physical Environment on Human Behavior, 1970; MS224.005.051.00017; Field, Hermann H. (Box 51)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine School of Dental Medicine A Plan to Meet Facility Needs, 1970; MS224.005.051.00018 (Box 51)
    - Development of the Tufts-New England Medical Center A Preliminary Study, 1965 -- 1985; MS224.005.051.00019 (Box 51)
    - Proceedings of A Special Conference on Health Facilities Research, 1970; MS224.005.051.00020 (Box 51)
    - Mental Health Coupling Project Grant Proposal, 1969; MS224.005.051.00021 (Box 51)
    - Adaptive Housing for the Handicapped, 1971; MS224.005.051.00022; Fishman, Paul L. (Box 51)
    - To Facilitate Health, A Proposal to Establish Health Facilities Research Inc., 1971; MS224.005.051.00023; Maloney, William F.; Pollack, Jerome; Field, Hermann H. (Box 51)
    - NECH Inpatient Admission Survey Report, 1969; MS224.005.051.00024 (Box 51)
    - Report on Recreation Facilities, 1967; MS224.005.051.00025 (Box 51)